{
  "listQuestions": [
    {
      "question": "It is the default row height of a single cell in MS Excel 2013.",
      "choices": [ "5", "10", "15", "20" ],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the company that owns Google?",
      "choices": [ "Gogle, Inc.", "Google LLC", "Alphabet Inc.", "Microsoft" ],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Which key can be used to view a slide show in MS Powerpoint?",
      "choices": [ "F5", "F2", "F7", "F9" ],
      "correct": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What tech company became America’s first trillion-dollar company?",
      "choices": [ "Microsoft", "Google", "Apple", "Samsung" ],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is known as the Father of Internet?",
      "choices": [ "Tim Berners-Lee", "Vint Cerf", "Charles Babbage", "James Gosling" ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "How much did the first handheld cell phone weigh?",
      "choices": [ "2lb", "2kg", "0.8kg", "1.23lb" ],
      "correct": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which general-purpose high-level programming language was created by Guido van Rossum in the Netherlands?",
      "choices": [ "C#", "Java", "C++", "Python" ],
      "correct": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "In MS Word, what picture layout option will give the photo its own line without any text on either side?",
      "choices": [ "In Line with text", "Top and Bottom", "Through", "Square" ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "In 1957, the first of the major languages appeared in the form of FORTRAN. What does FORTRAN stands for?",
      "choices": [ "Formula Translation", "Formula Translating", "Formula Transfiguration", "Formula Transition" ],
      "correct": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the capacity of a standard PC floppy?",
      "choices": [ "1.2MB", "1.44KB", "1.44MB", "120MB" ],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "What frequency range is the High Frequency band?",
      "choices": [ "100 kHz", "1GHz", "30 - 300 MHz", "3 - 30 MHz" ],
      "correct": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "McAfee, the internet security company, became a subsidiary of which of these in 2011?",
      "choices": [ "Intel", "Microsoft", "Dell", "IBM" ],
      "correct": 0
    }












  ]
}
